Guide to the Riverwalk Jazz Collection ARS.0129
Archive of Recorded Sound
- Radio relations files
  - Radio stations
    - stations, by call letters
      - KALW, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KAMU, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KANU, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KANW, 1 folder; 1 CD-R (Box 192)
      - KANZ, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KAOS, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KAZI, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KBCS, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KBEM, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KBPS, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KBRW, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KBSU, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KCCK, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KCLU, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KCPB, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KCRW, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KCSM, 1 folder; 2 CD-Rs (Box 192)
      - KCSN, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KEMC, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KERA, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KETR, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KFSK, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KHCC, 1 folder; 1 CD-R (Box 192)
      - KIAL, 1 folder; 1 CD-R (Box 192)
      - KIOS, 1 folder; 1 CD-R (Box 192)
      - KJAZ, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KJZZ, 2 folders (Box 192)
      - KKGO, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KLON, 5 folders; 1 computer disk (Box 192)
      - KLRN, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KMFA, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KMSU/KMSK, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KMUW, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KNCT, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KNOB, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KNOW, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KNTU, 1 folder; 1 CD-R (Box 192)
      - KOHM, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KOOP, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KPBS, 2 folders (Box 192)
      - KPLU, 1 folder (Box 192)
      - KPRG, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KQED, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KRCB, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KRCI, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KRCL, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KRML, 2 folders (Box 193)
      - KRPS, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KRTU, 2 folders (Box 193)
      - KSDS, 2 folders; 1 CD-R (Box 193)
      - KSKA, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KSMF, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KSTX, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KSUT, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KSVR, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KTEP, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KTPR, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KTSA, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KTSU, 2 folders; 1 CD-R (Box 193)
      - KTXK, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KUAT/KUAZ, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KUER, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KUFM/KGPR, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KUMR, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KUNI/KHKE, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KUNV, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KUSC, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KUSP, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KUVO, 1 folder; 1 CD-R [Cullum interview 9/29/2005] (Box 193)
      - KVLU, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KVPR, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KVRT, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KWBU, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KWGS, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KWIT, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KWMR, 1 folder; 1 computer disk (Box 193)
      - KWMU, 1 folder (Box 193)
      - KXJZ, 2 folders (Box 193)
      - WABE, 1 folder; 1 CD-R (Box 194)
      - WAMU, 1 folder (Box 194)
      - WAUS, 1 folder (Box 194)
      - WBAA, 1 folder (Box 194)
      - WBEZ, 1 folder (Box 194)
      - WBFO, 1 folder (Box 194)
      - WBGO, 2 folders; 1 CD-R (Box 194)
      - WBLV, 1 folder (Box 194)
      - WCBE, 1 folder (Box 194)
      - WCBU, 1 folder (Box 194)
      - WCPN, 1 folder (Box 194)
      - WCQS, 1 folder (Box 194)
      - WCVE, 2 folders; 2 CD-Rs (Box 194)
      - WDCB, 1 folder 2 CD-Rs (Box 194)
      - WDCU, 1 folder (Box 194)
      - WDNA, 1 folder 2 CD-Rs (Box 194)
      - WDUQ, 1 folder 2 CD-Rs (Box 194)
      - WETA, 1 folder (Box 194)
      - WEBR, 1 folder (Box 194)
      - WETS, 1 folder (Box 194)
      - WFAE, 1 folder (Box 194)
      - WFDD, 1 folder (Box 194)
      - WFIT, 1 folder (Box 194)
      - WFMT, 1 folder (Box 194)
      - WFPL, 1 folder (Box 194)
      - WFPK, 1 folder (Box 194)
      - WFUV, 1 folder (Box 194)
      - WGBH, 3 folders; 2 CD-Rs (Box 195)
      - WGVU, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WHRV, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WHYY, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WIAA, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WICR, 1 folder; 1 CD-R (Box 195)
      - WILL, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WISE, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WJCT, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WJFF, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WJHU, 1 folder; 1 CD-R (Box 195)
      - WKCR, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WKMS, 1 folder; 1 CD-R (Box 195)
      - WKNO, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WLIU/WCWP, 1 folder; 1 CD-R (Box 195)
      - WLRH, 1 folder; 1 CD-R (Box 195)
      - WMHT, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WMKV, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WMKY, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WMMT, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WMNR, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WMOT, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WMUB, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WNCW, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WNYC, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WOAI, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WOI, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WORT, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WOUB, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WPBX, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WPRL, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WQEW, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WRTI, 1 folder 1 CD-R (Box 195)
      - WRUV, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WRVG, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WSIE, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WSIU, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WSKG, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WTSU, 1 folder; 1 CD-R (Box 195)
      - WUCF, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WUGA, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WUKY, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WUIS, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WUNC, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WUOM, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WUWM, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WVAS, 1 folder; 1 CD-R (Box 195)
      - WVIA, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WVMR, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WVPE, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WVPN, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WVXU, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WWN, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WWNO, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WWOZ, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WXXI, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WYMS, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WYSU, 1 folder (Box 195)
      - WZRU, 1 folder (Box 195)
    - America One, 1 folder (Box 196)
    - Any Swing Goes Radio Show - San Diego, 1 folder (Box 197)
    - Canada: Jazz FM 91 - Toronto; CFUV, 2 folders; 2 CD-Rs (Box 196)
    - Carriage reports and correspondence, 1990-2001; 25 folders; 2 computer disks (Box 198, Box 199)
      Regular PRI reports of stations carrying RWJ, including market, frequency, and time slot. No files past 2001 (offically stopped printing 10/2000, available on ProNet system)
    - CPB Public Broadcasting Directory [annotated], 1 folder (Box 197)
    - General Radio, 1 folder (Box 197)
    - Los Angeles, 1 folder (Box 196)
    - Maine Public Broadcasting, 1 folder (Box 196)
    - miscellaneous radio, 1 folder (Box 196)
    - Nebraska Public Radio, 1 folder (Box 196)
    - Potential Affiliates, 14 folders (Box 196)
    - Prairie Public Radio, 1 folder (Box 196)
    - Promotions, 7 folders (Box 196)
    - Promotional Faxes: California, 1 folder (Box 197)
    - Ray Smith Radio Show, 1 folder (Box 197)
    - Satellite Distribution, 1 folder (Box 196)
    - SCERN, 1 folder (Box 196)
    - Station Relations, 3 folders (Box 197)
    - Station Interviews, 1 folder (Box 197)
    - Station Spots, 12 CD-Rs (Audio 134)
    - Target Stations, 2000; 21 folder (Box 197)
    - Wisconsin Public Radio, 1 folder (Box 196)
    - XM Public Radio, 1 folder (Box 196)
    - XSTAR Network, 1 folder (Box 196)
- Listener correspondence
  Fan mail, feedback and other responses, including facsmiles, email printouts, voicemail transcriptions, quiz answers from Catfish Club participants, and orders for products. Many exist in multiple copies, or were reused in promotional literature. Some are noted as "entered in database," which may exist on one of the hard drives. There is correspondence here from Norma Teagarden, Leonard Maltin, Bill Keane, and Bob Ringwald, among other notables.
  - Quotes, Endorsements, Testimonials, Press Kit Masters, 10 folders; 1 computer disk (Box 216)
  - Educational Letters, 1 folder (Box 216)
  - Replies, 6 folders (Box 216)
  - Miscellaneous Emails and Letters, 1999-2006; 1 folder (Box 216)
  - 1990-1992, 8 folders (Box 217)
  - 1992-1994, 7 folders (Box 218)
  - 1994-1998, 17 folders (Box 219)
  - 1998-2007, 7 folders (Box 220)
- Jim Cullum/Jim Cullum Jazz Band
  Chronicles activity by the Jim Cullum Jazz Band outside of Riverwalk, including press kits, reviews, tour information and recordings. Also includes writing and interview transcripts from Jim Cullum, and a few scores.
  - Jim Cullum writings [correspondence and essays], 3 folders (Box 245)
  - Letters From Jim's Memory Book At Summit, 1 folder (Box 245)
  - Imagineers Award, 1 folder (Box 245)
  - Jim Cullum Interview With Bill Celaya. Transcript, 1 folder; 1 audiocassette; 1 computer disk (Box 245)
  - JCJB 40th Anniversary, 1 folder (Box 245)
  - JCJB Cartoon, 1 folder (Box 245)
  - JCJB Live, 1 folder (Box 246)
  - JCJB Tune Lists, Research, 5 folders (Box 245)
  - JCJB Research General [article clippings], 1 folder (Box 246)
  - JCJB Stationery, 1 folder (Box 246)
  - Press Kits, 1 folder (Box 252)
  - Porgy and Bess, 2 folders (Box 245)
  - Storyville Records correspondence, 1 folder (Box 245)
  - Super Satch, 1 folder (Box 245)
  - article clippings, reviews, etc., 7 folders (Box 246)
  - Jim Cullum commercial releases
    While none are Riverwalk branded, some CDs, such as Hooray for Hoagy, Porgy and Bess and Super Satch. are related to RWJ programs.
    - Bob Barnard and Jim Cullum. Cornet Copia (La Brava Music LB0037), 2000; 1 compact disc (Audio 86)
    - Jim Cullum's Happy Jazz Band. Live and Swingin' (Jazzology JCD-252), 1995; 1 compact disc (Audio 86)
    - Jim Cullum's Happy Jazz. Live and Swingin.' Hot Jazz Performances From The Landing (A+R, Dallas Texas), 1 audiocassette (Audio 135)
    - Jim Cullum Jazz Band. Hooray For Hoagy! (Audiophile ACD-251), 1990; 1 compact disc (Audio 86)
    - Jim Cullum Jazz Band. Hooray For Hoagy! (Audiophile AC-251), 1 audiocassette (Audio 135)
    - Jim Cullum Jazz Band. Hot (Jazzology JCD-354), 2006; 1 compact disc (Audio 86)
    - Jim Cullum Jazz Band. Live at the Memphis Jazz Festival (Jazzology JCD-132), 1 compact disc (Audio 86)
    - Jim Cullum Jazz Band. Porgy and Bess. Jazz Transcription. Demo, 1 audiocassette (Audio 135)
    - Jim Cullum Jazz Band. Porgy and Bess (CBS FMT 42517), 1987; 1 audiocassette (Audio 135)
    - Jim Cullum Jazz Band. Porgy and Bess (CBS MK 42517), 1987; 1 compact disc (Audio 86)
    - Jim Cullum Jazz Band. Shootin' The Agate. Music of Jelly Roll Morton (Stomp Off C1254), 1993; 1 audiocassette (Audio 135)
    - Jim Cullum Jazz Band. Shootin' The Agate. Music of Jelly Roll Morton (Stomp Off CD1254), 1993; 1 compact disc (Audio 87)
    - Jim Cullum Jazz Band. SUPER SATCH (Stomp Off C1148), 1 audiocassette (Audio 135)
    - Jim Cullum Jazz Band. SUPER SATCH (Stomp Off CD1148), 1 compact disc (Audio 86)
    - Jim Cullum Jazz Band. Tis The Season...To Be Jammin' (Summit World Jazz Recordings SWJCD-21), 1 compact disc (Audio 87)
    - Jim Cullum Jazz Band. Tis The Season...To Be Jammin' (World Jazz Recordings WJLP S-21), 1 audiocassette (Audio 135)
    - Jim Cullum's Jazz Band With Bobby Hackett. Goose Pimples (Jazzology JCD-331), 2003; 1 compact disc (Audio 86)
    - The Newton Boys. Music From The Motion Picture (Epic/Sony Soundtrax EK69182) ["Featuring Riverwalk's Jim Cullum Jazz Band" -- sticker on shrinkwrap], 1 compact disc (Audio 86)
    - The Newton Boys. Music From The Motion Picture. Promotional Copy - Not For Sale (Sony Music Enterntainment), 1998; 1 audiocassette (Audio 135)
    - Still Breathing. Score Selections (Zap Pictures), 1 audiocassette (Audio 135)
    - Soundtrack To The Motion Picture Still Breathing (Will Records Wil049) ["Featuring Riverwalk's Jim Cullum Jazz Band" -- sticker on shrinkwrap], 1998; 1 compact disc (Audio 86)
    - Ralph Sutton and Jim Cullum. Long Ways From St. Louis (Gaslight Records GSL-5004) "Produced and manufactured under license from Riverwalk Jazz Project", 2002; 1 compact disc (Audio 86)
  - Sheet music
    - Nightspell, 1 folder; 1 CD-R (Box 140)
    - December Landing Music, Bria Show [manuscript], 1 folder (Box 140)
    - Other Music, 1 folder (Box 140)
- Jazz education
  Reports and proposals related to Riverwalk and Jim Cullum's jazz education intitiatives. Most material was not donated.
  - Jazz Education, 2 folders (Box 246)
  - Jazz Education Outreach Project: Kronkosky Charitable Foundation, 2 folders (Box 246)
  - Jim Cullum Jazz Video Curriculum, 4 folders (Box 246)
  - Sun Production Music Education Promotion Research, 1 folder (Box 246)
  - Riverwalk Jazz Early Childhood Education Project, 1 folder (Box 246)
- Riverwalk National Advisory Board, 1989-2009
  Files regarding Advisory Board activity from 1989 to 2009, including reports, agendas, fundraising and other event planning and publicity, correspondence (inc. "group letters and packets" address lists), and promotional packets. Only one set of minutes is present, for the 2/27/2006 meeting.
  - 1989-1993, 29 folders (Box 161)
  - 1993, 17 folders (Box 156)
  - 1993-1995, 24 folders (Box 157)
  - 1995-1998, 15 folders (Box 158)
  - 1999-2001, 11 folder (Box 159)
  - 2002-2005, 11 folder (Box 160)
  - 2006-2009, 9 folders (Box 202)
- Sponsors, grants and fundraising
  Files and recordings concerning Riverwalk's funding sources, including sponsors (espcially See's Candies), fundraising efforts, and grants.
  - See's Candies, 1988-2006
    - Charles Huggins, 5 folders (Box 205)
    - Catalogs and related correspondence, 2 folders (Box 205)
    - PR/Promotion, 9 folders (Box 205)
    - Riverwalk Funder files [correspondence and memoranda], 15 folders (Box 206)
    - Annual reports, contracts and related files, 1997-2006; 23 folders (Box 206, Box 207, Box 208)
    - See's Theme/Jingle, 4 folders (Box 208)
    - See's Book by Margaret Pick, 16 folders (Box 209)
    - Recordings
      See's Candies sponsored Riverwalk until 2006. Promotional compact discs with production material, interviews with Charles Huggins and Dick Van Auren in 2004
      - Bix's 100th Birthday. A Special Riverwalk Jazz Production For See's Candies, 2003; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 84)
      - California Report, 2006-02-10; 1 CD-R (Audio 84)
      - Demo CD for See's Master, 1 CD-R (Audio 84)
      - Bud Freeman and Summa Cum Laude Swing, 2005; 1 CD-R (Audio 84)
      - From the Heart, The Music of Louis Armstrong. A Special Riverwalk Jazz Production For See's Candies, 2005; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 84)
      - The Genius of Jelly Roll Morton, 2005; 1 CD-R (Audio 84)
      - Holiday Spectacular. A Seasonal Riverwalk Jazz Production For See's Candies, 2004; 1 CD-R (Audio 84)
      - Home for The Holidays: A Seasonal Riverwalk Jazz Production For See's Candies, 2003-2005; 3 CD-Rs (Audio 84)
      - Jazz For A Mellow Mood. A Special Production For See's Candies, 2 CD-Rs (Audio 84)
      - Muggsy Spanier. A Special Riverwalk Jazz Production For See's Candies, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 84)
      - Seasonal CD for See's Candies, 2 CD-Rs (Audio 84)
      - Just A little Bit Of Sweetness (Theme), 2 audiocassettes (Audio 84)
      - See's Theme, 1 audiocassette (Audio 138)
      - See's Candy Audio Interview. Charles Huggins, 2004-06-16; 3 DATs; 4 CD-Rs (Audio 79)
      - See's Candy Audio Interview. Dick Van Auren (Senior Vice-President of Marketing), 2004-08-16; 1 DAT; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 79)
      - Voice of God, See's, 2003-07-16; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
      - See's ID Credits, 2005-03-01; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
      - See's Radio. Easter Holiday Orchestra :60, 1 audiocassette (Audio 136)
      - 3 See's Promos with JCJB, 1 audiocassette (Audio 136)
      - New See's Candy Jingle. Edited Version, 1 audiocassette (Audio 136)
  - Mission Pharmacal, 2005-2008
    - Annual Reports and notes, 6 folders (Box 210)
    - Bayer, 1 folder (Box 210)
    - Mission Pharmacal Citracal Preliminary Spots, 2003-05-13; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Citracal: Creamy Bites Mock Credit ID Tags, 1 CD-R (Audio 87)
    - Mission Pharm CD v.3, 1 CD-R (Audio 87)
    - Mission CD; Mission Pharm v.4, 2 CD-Rs (Audio 87)
    - Mission Report - Broadcast Archive Binder [CD-Rs of programs with printouts of home page and JazzNotes for 39 weeks 2006-2007], 1 folder; 35 CD-Rs (Box 250)
  - Sun Products Corporation/All
    - Sun Products Broadcast Credits. JCJB, All, 1 CD-R (Audio 87)
    - Sun Update [report], 2010; 1 folder (Box 211)
    - Sun/Neil Defeo, 2008; 1 folder (Box 211)
    - Reports, correspondence, etc., 2008-2009; 6 folders (Box 211, Box 210)
    - Sun Products press, 1 folder (Box 210)
    - Guenther, 1 folder (Box 210)
    - Sun Promotions, 1 folder (Box 210)
  - Fundraising sources, 46 folders (Box 211, Box 212)
    Files involving corporate and individual donors, foundations, and charitable trusts, most from a series identified as "Hot Funders." Includes proposals for special projects, especially jazz education (see also the Jazz Education series).
  - Fundraising production files
    Fundraising shows and spots. also solicitation/ie direct mail campaigning. scripts, correspondence, notes. premiums.
    - Fundraising report, 2008; 1 folder (Box 253)
    - On-Air Fundraising Survey, 2000; 1 folder (Box 253)
    - Station Fundraising, 1 folder (Box 253)
    - 1993-2000 Funders, 20 folders; 3 computer disks; 1 2CD set [PRI Best of Fundraising 1999] (Box 254, Box 253)
    - 2001-2003 Funders, 12 folders; 4 CD-Rs (Box 255)
    - 2004-2007 Funders, 12 folders; 25 CD-Rs (Box 256)
    - 2007-2010 Funders, 1 folder; 6 CD-Rs (Box 257)
    - Fundraiser shows
      Segments, pitches, promos, etc. Organized chronologically.
      - Spring Fundraising Script, 1 audiocassette (Audio 135)
      - Fundraiser, 1993; 2 DATs (Audio 49)
      - Fall Fundraiser, 1993; 1 audiocassette (Audio 135)
      - Fundraiser, 1994; 1 DAT (Audio 49)
      - Fundraiser, 1995; 1 DAT (Audio 49)
      - Live From The West Coast. #14 Fundraiser, 1995; 1 audiocassette (Audio 135)
      - Fall Fundraising Package Suggestions, 1996; 1 audiocassette (Audio 135)
      - Fundraiser, 1996; 1 audiocassette (Audio 135)
      - Fundraiser, 1996; 2 DATs (Audio 49)
      - Fundraiser, 1997; 2 DATs (Audio 49)
      - Fundraiser, 1998; 1 DAT (Audio 49)
      - Fall Fundraiser Modules, 1999; 4 DATs (Audio 49)
      - Spring Fundraising, 2000; 3 DATs (Audio 49)
      - Fall Fundraiser, 2000; 3 DATs; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 49, Audio 84)
      - Spring Fundraiser, 2001; 3 DATs (Audio 49)
      - Fall Fundraiser, 2001; 3 DATs; 1 CD-R (Audio 49, Audio 84)
      - Spring Fundraiser, 2002; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 84)
      - Fall Fundraiser, 2002; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 84)
      - Spring Fundraiser, 2003; 4 CD-Rs (Audio 84)
      - Fall Fundraiser, 2003; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 84)
      - Spring Fundraiser, 2004; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 84)
      - Fall Fundraiser, 2004; 3 CD-Rs (Audio 84)
      - Fall Fundraiser. JCJB With Vernel Bagneris. From The Heart: Louis Armstrong Remembers, 2005; 3 CD-Rs (Audio 84)
      - Fall Fundraiser. JCJB. Jelly Roll Morton: World's Greatest Hot Tune Writer, 2005; 1 CD-R (Audio 84)
      - Spring Fundraiser. JCJB. Chasin' The Blues, 2006; 1 CD-R (Audio 84)
      - Spring Fundraiser, 2007; 1 CD-R (Audio 84)
      - Fall Fundraiser. JCJB. Old-school Jazz Swings Russia, 2007; 1 CD-R (Audio 84)
      - Old-School Jazz Swings Russia. The Jim Cullum Jazz Band. High-Voltage Fundraising Program. Riverwalk Jazz Fall Fundraising Materials [disc is affixed to postcard], 2007; 1 compact disc (Audio 79)
      - Fall Fundraiser, 2008; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 84)
      - SP10 Funder and Promo Spots [2010?], 1 CD-R (Audio 84, Box 84)
    - fundraising discs
      - Akron Foundation, 1992; 1 computer disk (Box 43)
      - GAR Foundation, 1991-1996; 13 computer disks (Box 43)
      - Marlboro Trust, 1991-1993; 1 computer disk (Box 43)
  - Grants
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1999-2000; 5 folders (Box 212)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 2002-2006; 12 folders (Box 213, Box 212)
    - NEA Work Samples, 2003-2007; 6 CD-Rs (Audio 88)
- Marketing and promotion
  - Award applications
    - AFIM, 1 folder (Box 204)
    - CPB, 1 folder (Box 204)
    - Gabriel, 1 folder (Box 204)
    - GRAMMY, 1 folder (Box 204)
    - New York Radio Festival, 1 folder (Box 204)
    - Ohio State, 1 folder (Box 204)
    - Peabody, 1 folder (Box 204)
    - Third Coast, 1 folder (Box 204)
  - Catfish Club, 1 folder (Box 259)
  - Demographics and market research reports
    Some reports are specifically about Riverwalk, others are about general public radio consumption habits and patterns.
    - Arbitron PVP, 1 folder (Box 229)
    - Audience 98: Audience Research Analysis (CPB), 1998; 1 folder (Box 229)
    - Audigraphics Consulation Guide, 1998; 1 folder (Box 229)
    - NPR Audience and Corporate Research, 1 folder (Box 229)
    - Profile 94 (NPR), 1994; 1 folder (Box 229)
    - Program Marketing Report, 2002; 1 folder (Box 230)
    - PRPD Jazz Core Values, 1 folder (Box 229)
    - SRG Public Radio Profile, 2005; 1 folder (Box 229)
    - 1986-1998, 11 folders (Box 229)
    - 1998-2003, 10 folders (Box 230)
    - 2004-2009, 8 folders (Box 231)
  - Hot 100 Club, 2 folders (Box 259)
  - Jazz Appreciation Month, 2 folders (Box 259)
  - Jim Cullum Jazz Band Promos, 1 folder (Box 259)
  - Chris Langer, 2 folders (Box 260)
  - Leonard Maltin, 1 folder (Box 260)
  - Mayoral Letter [Nelson Wolff to Sydney Barthelemy re: Battle of the Bands], 1994; 1 folder (Box 260)
  - Media Buy, 1 folder (Box 260)
  - misc. promo correspondence, etc., 1989-2008; 10 folders (Box 258)
  - Mspot, 1 folder (Box 260)
  - Outreach - Jazz Organizations
    - American Federation of Jazz Societies, 1 folder (Box 188)
    - Kansas City Jazz International, 3 folders (Box 188)
    - Madison Jazz Society, 2 folders (Box 188)
    - National Jazz Service Organization, 1 folder (Box 188)
    - New Jersey Jazz Society, 1 folder (Box 188)
    - misc. society outreach/marketing, 1 folder (Box 188)
  - PBS "Jazz" Cross-promotion, 1 folder (Box 260)
  - Press kits
    - 1988, 1 folder (Box 248)
    - 1989, 3 folders (Box 248)
    - 1990, 1 folder (Box 248)
    - 1991, 3 folders (Box 248)
    - 1992, 4 folders (Box 248)
    - 1993, 8 folders; 1 computer disk (Box 248)
    - 1994, 5 folders (Box 249)
    - 1995, 3 folders (Box 249)
    - 1996, 3 folders (Box 249)
    - 1997, 1 folder (Box 249)
    - 1998, 4 folders (Box 250)
    - Bromley Communications [mostly JazzNotes printouts], 2005-2006; 1 folder (Box 250)
    - American Public Media, 2007-04; 1 folder (Box 250)
    - Jim Cullum's Riverwalk Jazz Intellectual Property Assets, 2009-04; 1 folder; 4 CDS-Rs (Box 250)
    - 20th Anniversary, 2009; 4 folders; 4 CD-Rs (Box 250)
  - Press releases, 1990-2000; 7 folders (Box 260)
  - PRC Postcard, 1 folder (Box 260)
  - PRI Promo, 1995; 1 folder (Box 260)
  - PRI. Salyer Endorsement, 1994; 1 folder (Box 260)
  - Promo and credits production files, 1996-2001; 20 folders; 1 computer disk (Box 253)
    Scripts and correspondence involved in the production of promotional ads and credits for programs and products. The promos are either generic or customized for radio stations. Two promos were made for each show; one with music, one voice only. For recordings, see Program Production Recording Elements.
  - Promotional postcards, handbills, etc., 1 folder (Box 257)
  - Protocol Communications, 5 folders (Box 260)
  - Public Interactive - Gottlieb, 2001; 2 folders (Box 261)
  - Public Radio Cookbook, 1 folder (Box 261)
  - Publicity
    Riverwalk press in the form of articles, reviews and advertisements. Also includes concert programs, catalog listings, printouts from the web, and some correspondence. Many are from the San Antonio Express News. See also press under Jim Cullum Jazz Band.
    - misc. clippings, articles, advertisements. originals, photocopies, printouts, 16 folders (Box 190)
    - Newspapers [oversize], 1 folder (Box 78)
    - Press correspondence, 1 folder (Box 190)
    - Advertising, 1994-1995; 1 folder; 1 computer disk (Box 257)
    - American Rag, 1996-2000; 2 folders (Box 191)